Bon appétit!
It's so delicious!
Look at this!
Looks so good!
I love it!
Yum! Yum!
Yummy?
Yes, it is.
Hello everyone! This is Mino Motono and Shizuki Yamashita from Sakurazaka 46.
This time, as is becoming a bit of a tradition, we'd like to share with you the third ramen project.
The Osaka leg of this tour ended yesterday, and the next day we decided to enjoy Osaka's ramen a little more.
We did the same as we did in Fukuoka.
I'm looking forward to it, because I haven't found the ramen of Osaka yet!
I'm looking forward to seeing you soon!
I bought a camera.
I bought a camera and I'm going to start taking pictures of ramen!
I'm going to start today.
I thought I'd take some good shots.
Here we are!
Ta-da!
Chinese noodles!
We're at Kadoya Shokudo!
Again!
We both ordered Chinese soba noodles!
I guess it's the most standard one!
I could often search for a pair of skates!
It was a popular shoe in the picture
Yes, here you go. Chinese soba noodles.
It's here.
Yay!
It looks so delicious.
It looks delicious.
The barley.
Thank you for watching.
Oh, there was something I caught up on.
Seino, yes. Bon appétit.
Looks delicious.
It smells so good.
I could smell it even from outside the restaurant.
I'll have some soup.
A large bowl of beef soba noodles, topped with Himami.
It's very tasty. It's like soy sauce.
The noodles are also sticky.
Mochi Mochi. They are shiny and glossy.
It's so delicious!
I was so surprised.
It's slippery, isn't it?
The surface is slippery.
Fine noodles.
Delicious!
It's so good!
I think I can smell it.
I'm sure it's true.
It's so good.
I really like the noodles.
They're so smooth.
There's some pickled bamboo shoots in there, too.
What is that? Is that kikurage?
Menma? What?
What, glitter?
Did you do that?
You got it?
The chashu is amazing.
It's like a baan-kuchen.
It's different from other chashu pork I've had.
It's a little different from other chashu pork I've had.
Bon appétit!
I don't think I've ever tasted anything like this before.
This is the first time I've had this flavor of chashu.
It tastes so good!
It's packed with flavor.
Dark chashu pork
I like it best with nori (seaweed)
Thank you very much for the food.
Thank you for watching!
Delicious?
Delicious? Yes, it is.
Thank you for watching.
In the store, of course.
Maschere Choux.
Thank you for watching.
Very tasty.
Yes, I mean...
I just finished eating it.
Thank you very much for the food.
Thank you for the food.
It was delicious.
It was so good!
It's not like the ramen I usually eat.
Soy sauce or something like that
This soup looks so delicious!
It was really, really good!
I want noodles, personally.
5 points out.
If you like slippery, thin noodles
I really hope you go there.
Maybe it's a personal thing, but
One bowl is quite filling.
It's very filling.
I'm sorry.
It's quite filling.
Yes, it is.
When I greeted you.
Bring your camera.
I'll take a picture of the ramen.
I was able to take pictures from this time.
Why was it taken?
LOL.
I was too busy eating.
I'm so sorry.
Let me have my revenge next time!
Please take my picture!
The second restaurant is here!
We came to Strike Ticket!
Another Chinese noodle shop!
It's got a baseball or something on it.
Okay, the second one, too!
Let's go!
This is the type of meal ticket!
Amazing!
I'll have a straight wave.
What color?
You like it.
You said you wanted to have it again tomorrow.
I don't know.
Let's have it again tomorrow.
Wait a minute, please.
Just give me 10 more seconds.
Yeah, sure.
Miyogakko.
Let's go.
I'm going.
I'll go.
I'll put the money in.
You're putting it in first?
That's good.
This way.
I can't put it in here.
I don't know if this is gonna work.
Here we go.
Yay!
Bon appétit!
Thank you for watching.
Here you go. Straight rounds.
Here you go.
Here you go, sir. Straight up, with ajitama.
That's it!
Ta-da! Here it comes!
Ta-da!
This is the straight wave.
This is the straight wave with ajitama
Look at this!
Looks delicious!
The fat is stuck!
Puya-puya!
Looks delicious, doesn't it?
Welcome, bye-bye!
So cute
Every time I'm in a role this good
May I take a picture for the camera?
Here you go, take a picture.
Finally, I can take a picture.
Looks delicious
Okay, let's have a look, guys.
So cute.
Ah!
Okay, sure.
Okay, now that we've finally accomplished that, let's have some fun!
Yum! Yum!
Delicious!
I think the noodles are thicker than at the other restaurant.
Yes, they are thicker!
They are here to make a special ishinger fried chicken!
Delicious!
Nori-like?
Nori salad
Taste
Oh, there's nori in it again.
Yes, it's there.
Isn't there seaweed in chuka soba?
Yes, it does.
There's pickled bamboo shoots too. Not pickled bamboo shoots. Naruto.
Delicious.
It's so good!
Delicious!
I think it's some kind of noodle with great elasticity, and I think it's something thicker than ramen noodles
Not thin noodles.
I like this kind of taste in everything.
That's why I like it so much.
Delicious!
It's so good!
The taste is totally different from before.
The thickness is different.
It's not as thick, and it's not as thick as before, and it tastes like soup.
The taste of meat is quite strong.
This is so delicious!
Ajitama, ajitama, ajitama!
Is it good?
It goes well with ramen.
Ramen.
Let's think of something to go with ramen.
Wait...
One thing that's not ramen at all.
We had a competition once... over baked sweet potatoes and ice cream or kimchi.
Which do you prefer?
I think Yutaka Shima is more of an ice cream guy.
And Kanibu-chan is more in favor of kimchi with baked sweet potato.
And we were arguing a lot.
I'm a kimchi person.
But Yuchan Murai is an ice cream fan.
But it's so rich, isn't it?
It's very strong.
You know? You know?
Kimchi.
It's sweet.
It's the same.
Noodles and potatoes.
Tasty?
Yes, it's good.
You can't imagine what sweet potato with noodles tastes like.
But I thought ramen noodles and vanilla ice cream would go well together.
I'm kind of obsessed with food.
I thought I was the only one who could pair this with that.
Maybe not.
No, I don't.
I'm unusual in one way.
I can pair any drink with any food.
It's only food.
You're lying.
What do you think?
You can drink coffee with ramen?
I can't have coffee with coffee.
Boring.
You're killing my project.
Sorry.
Let's talk about our hobbies.
When we're not working...
We're into Horror Aid films.
We often watch them together.
With half the earphones in.
Suddenly you're backstage yelling.
What are you talking about?
He was a little angry with me.
I had to interrupt him to stop him from talking.
I was watching him.
Mr. Kamimura said.
"What are you doing?" He said.
"What's going on?" "What's wrong?
"What's wrong?" and "What's wrong?" He was so cute.
From the outside, they thought I was weird.
I can't go to abandoned places.
I can't go to places I trust.
Mr. Fujiyoshi said...
Fujikichi said he likes abandoned buildings.
I saw an article about you going to an abandoned building.
I was curious, so I asked him...
"You went to the ruins, didn't you?" I said, "Yes.
He said he did.
I asked him, "Do you like ghosts?" I asked him.
He didn't.
He said he liked abandoned buildings.
I wonder why.
I think I'm eating Naruto for the first time.
He draws them a lot in his illustrations.
He draws them on his araf characters.
On the ramen cat.
But I've never eaten it.
But there's a stuffed Naruto on it.
I'll have some.
Stuffed Naruto
It tastes just as I imagined, this is the first time I've had Naruto
What is this? What is it, Naruto?
Is it a fish paste? It's not fish paste.
It tastes like fish paste.
Kamaboko?
This is Naruto, for sure.
It's the pattern.
This... This has nothing to do with ramen...
I don't know...
I'm getting more and more obvious that I'm not very smart.
I've never had ramen noodles... salt ramen or miso?
Miso?
What's miso? Hokkaido?
Hokkaido.
I don't think I'll ever go to Hokkaido for ramen.
I'll have to go tour Hokkaido.
That's for sure.
I just realized that this year, there's a lot of lunch seating and...
There's a lot of equipment to buy, a lot of jewelry to buy.
So many people want to come and see the show.
Yeah.
It makes me very happy, and I can do my best because people think so.
I feel like...
Thank you for the food.
I'm very happy.
I'm so happy.
Thanks for the food. It's so simple.
Wait a minute.
I was wondering if you'd like to join us for dinner.
Yeah, sorry.
I'm sorry.
But it's only the beginning of the year, right?
Yeah. - Yeah.
It's just really started.
Yeah.
We're happy to be able to announce all kinds of fun things, so...
I'd like to do my best to make many more announcements this year 2024.
Yes.
We'll do our best too.
Right?
Yes.
I want to do my best to be involved in good news.
Yeah, let's do our best.
And that's the last chashu.
All right.
Oh, yummy!
Good job.
I know what you mean.
You got it.
Yeah. - Yeah.
It's cold.
Yeah, hold on.
One more.
All right.
I can't chew, but here.
Okay, I'm done eating.
Thanks for the food just now.
This time it's the third ramen project of ours
We went to two ramen shops in Osaka that were on our tour.
We went to two ramen stores in Osaka, where we had been on our tour.
It was really delicious!
It was yogurt!
Yes, I'd like to have some too.
It was really delicious.
It was delicious.
Not only pork bones like this.
I'd like to try all kinds of things.
Even from now on.
Yes, and there are many ramen that we haven't tried yet.
There are a lot of ramen that we haven't tried yet.
We will have opportunities to go to various areas in the future.
We are looking forward to the possibility that we may be able to eat ramen again in the future.
We hope to have another ramen project with you and us in mind.
I hope we can do another ramen project in the future.
Please subscribe to our channel and give us a high rating!
Bye bye!
I will eat again!
I want to eat it.